Seraphas (not to be confused with the Seraphim) are powerful air spirits that characterize Ylath's harshest nature, appearing in the form of great tornadoes, hitting everything they encounter in their path. A similar role they take on the battlefield, where they cut the enemies of their faith. Although the very fact of the appearance of these mighty elements filled the followers of the Dragon of Hope, many look anxiously at Seraphim, seeing in them the new church built in Ylatha, with their own hierarchy, soldiers, saints, and fanatics.