Elrath's radiant dominance is filled with numerous beings, and the rarest of them is the race of angels. With their help, the Dragon of Light has repeatedly contacted people, even by making a pact with them, when the legendary angels Sara and Uriel made the Holy Falcon empire with the consent of the Emperor. Archangels are the strongest of the angels, adapted to fight the forces of Darkness and Chaos. Now that another war is coming, the Empire could not cope without the help of those dedicated Elrath servants.